<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>life on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/life/</link><description>Recent content in life on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 01:08:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Still Here People...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/still-here-people/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 01:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/still-here-people/</guid><description>Yep, I am still here on this site. I was having a few problems with my webhost earlier this month, but those should all be resolved by now. (I hope!)
Whats new in my life you ask&amp;hellip; well lets see:
Completed a Data Center re-cabling job in less than 72 hours! That was no easy feat, involving most of my staff to give up a weekend to get it done. Looks great though, I will have to put up some photos of the finished product.</description></item><item><title>Lets try that again...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/lets-try-that-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 07:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/lets-try-that-again/</guid><description>I am happy to announce the re-opening of this blog! ~w00t! :)
A special Thank You to my new provider Hosting Puppy for the site &amp;amp; the fantastic support.
After 3 unsuccessful hosting providers and 2 site-wide data corruption issues, one would think that I would learn from my mistakes.
Oh well, 4th times the charm!
The only good news is that I am now extremely perficent at re-building my Wordpress site.</description></item><item><title>I'm Back!!</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2005/i-am-back/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2005 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2005/i-am-back/</guid><description>Its been awhile&amp;hellip; and all I can say is Im Back!
I have been extremely busy for the past year, what with the massive undertaking of my Companies Sarbanes-Oxley compliance, and managing the entire department while our new Director got up to speed. Not an easy task!
But now I&amp;rsquo;m back&amp;hellip; and I plan to put this blog to good use!
So&amp;hellip; to start of on the right foot, I am going to be documenting one of my many projects:</description></item><item><title>Special Birthday Present!!</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2004/special-birthday-present/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2004 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2004/special-birthday-present/</guid><description>I finally did it!!
As a Birthday Present for my 29th Birthday (Today.), my wife bought me a motorcycle.
(Can you believe it?? What a Gal!)
I have been_ pining_ for an older bike, so I can fix it up and not have to worry about some serious monetary commitments.
Well for $1400 and the cost of a 2XL helmet&amp;hellip; (I have a BIG F%^&amp;amp; HEAD!!), I am the proud owner of a 1965 BSA A65 Rocket.</description></item><item><title>Friends, Parting is such Sweet Sorrow...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2003/friends-parting-is-such-sweet-sorrow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2003 00:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2003/friends-parting-is-such-sweet-sorrow/</guid><description>Man, I am so bummed out!
Gerald (G-Dog, or EvilSkill9), my right hand-man for like 8 years has left California.
He is heading east, out to Ohio to start a new life with his girl.
Good for him&amp;hellip;. but I allready miss the bastard!
I can&amp;rsquo;t even imagine what our phone bills are going to be like. 😄
The reality has just kicked in, but I am a little far from sobbing&amp;hellip; 😢</description></item><item><title>Infectious Grooves</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2003/infectious-grooves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2003 01:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2003/infectious-grooves/</guid><description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that I am still so sick!
This really sucks&amp;hellip;
Although, the thought of walking around @ Work and Infecting innocent bystanders with whatever pestilence I have growing inside of me is amusing!
I wonder if I would get fired for sending my Boss home sick? I might just go wipe my nose all over his hankerchief (sic).
There is a reason why I should stay home when I am like this&amp;hellip; I have lots of Evil Thoughts like these!</description></item></channel></rss>