<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>review on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/review/</link><description>Recent content in review on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 21:15:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Golden Monkey</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/golden-monkey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 21:15:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/golden-monkey/</guid><description>Wifey said that I was stressed recently, and that we should go have a dinner date. God I love her, and would not know what to do without her!
She suggested that I pick the Place &amp;amp; Food (Generally this is a long discussion/argument for what to eat!), and I suggested that I wanted a really good hamburger! She had never been to Rodeo Goat , and I had a hankering for Chorizo and Beef!</description></item><item><title>Logic Bomb</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/logic-bomb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 10:13:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/logic-bomb/</guid><description>Back to relaxing in Upper Peninsula, and enjoying mild 80℉ weather for my 4th of July weekend!
Picked up some Surly Brewing Company&amp;rsquo;s Logic Bomb Juicy Pale Ale from the local Super One Foods &amp;hellip; my favorite local grocery store. Super One&amp;rsquo;s remind me of Piggy Wigley&amp;rsquo;s, which also only exist in the North-Mid-West for some reason!
Super tasty, and good for cooling you off while grilling. Steaks were delicious, and did not last long.</description></item><item><title>Long Strange Trip</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/long-strange-trip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 21:22:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/long-strange-trip/</guid><description>So, I like beer&amp;hellip; good beer. My tastes have changed over the years, and I am more of a social drinker now, but I still enjoy my liquid bread!
I tend to gravitate towards Hazy &amp;amp; Double IPA&amp;rsquo;s, but one of my all-time favorites types of beers is Belgian Tripel&amp;rsquo;s. My absolute special being the St. Bernardus Abt 12, which is actually a Belgian Quad!
I am not alone in that sentiment, as it is widely regarded as one of the best beers in the world.</description></item><item><title>Ski Jump IPA</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2021/ski-jump-ipa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 18:15:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2021/ski-jump-ipa/</guid><description>Hoppy IPA&amp;rsquo;s are just damn refreshing! I tend to like Hop-Forward IPA&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; as well as Hazy&amp;rsquo;s. A good strong flavor, without a huge bitter bite is more my style.
As a Newcomer to the UP area, I have been exploring the local breweries in the area for hidden jems! So far, I have been impressed with the selections including the 51st State Brewing Company !
The pub food is excellent. I would suggest their Pizza&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; as they are cooked in a wood fired oven.</description></item></channel></rss>