<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hacking on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/hacking/</link><description>Recent content in hacking on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 19:18:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/hacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Max Headroom Pirating Incident</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/the-max-headroom-pirating-incident/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 19:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/the-max-headroom-pirating-incident/</guid><description>Really interesting Documentary on the incident. Kind of makes you think about that struggle between Broadcasting Companies, and the Jackers who wanted to take over their airwaves.
I would assume that this trick is still possible in 3rd-World countries where the Media does not have the $$$ like US Broadcasters.
Plus&amp;hellip; Max Headroom was an awesome show! I miss a lot of the older/weirder shows from my youth.</description></item><item><title>The Binchotan Stove</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/binchotan-stove/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 19:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/binchotan-stove/</guid><description>Really cool stuff. I will have to try and make one of these. Binchotan is really expensive in this part of the country though!!</description></item><item><title>Auditor</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2005/auditor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2005 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2005/auditor/</guid><description>Found a very intresting piece of software called &amp;ldquo;Auditor&amp;rdquo;. (Actually its a compilation of software, on a bootable CD) Its bascially a rip of Kanotix, (Knoppix Clone) with a LOT of applications. Most notable is a copy of Kismet &amp;amp; Airdump. With these tools, you can WarDive an almost brute-force your way into a wi-fi network. Pretty cool. =D
I will be trying this later on!!!
Here is a link to the &amp;ldquo;Auditor&amp;rdquo; webpage&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>The Darknet Project</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2004/the-darknet-project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2004 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2004/the-darknet-project/</guid><description>Those Guys over at Team Cymru Research have done it again!
They have released a new version of their Darknet Project. For those unaware of what this is&amp;hellip; check it out!
Tracking compromised machines can be difficult. Security solutions often don&amp;rsquo;t scale to the size of larger networks. Technologies such as IDS are flawed, producing copious false positives. When solutions are scaled to fit the larger providers, they often require considerable care and feeding, thus taking time away from problem mitigation.</description></item></channel></rss>