<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>website on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/website/</link><description>Recent content in website on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:57:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Obsidian to Manage the Blog</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/using-obsidian-to-manage-the-blog/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:57:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2022/using-obsidian-to-manage-the-blog/</guid><description>![](/uploads/Pasted image 20221030011354.png)
I just recently started using Obsidian to manage my Work and Personal notes, and its pretty awesome. Obsidian is a powerful and extensible knowledge base that works on top of your local folder of plain text files.
![](/uploads/Pasted image 20221030011438.png)
Had a random thought this evening, and wonderd if anyone had ever used Obsidian to manage their Hugo-Based Blog. Looks like there are a few, but each implementation seems to differ wildly.</description></item><item><title>Move to Hugo</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2021/move-to-hugo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 20:48:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2021/move-to-hugo/</guid><description>So this site has long be running on an older branch of a Jekyll theme, that was heavly modified. I have always had problems updating the site, not to mention getting Jekyll to run properly on Windows. Also, I am not a real fan of Ruby.
Last year during our horrible dark times, I set out to learn a new programming language. I had been messing with Golang for a little while, and I finally sat down with some awesome online classes from PluralSight, and really got to task.</description></item><item><title>New Domain, New Rules</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2016/new-domain-new-rules/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 13:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2016/new-domain-new-rules/</guid><description>So here we are&amp;hellip; After trying to keep this thing alive for way to long, I have decided to give it another shot.
So much of this site is my own personal musings and ramblings, that I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I even remember where I was headed in the first place. I do have some interesting old posts, specifically about storage, tapes, and the cloud. Might be worth a read for someone.</description></item><item><title>Old Fortune City Site</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2010/old-fortune-city-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 17:58:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2010/old-fortune-city-site/</guid><description>While reviewing some of my old Hard-drives, I discovered that I had and copy of a site that I had build on Fortune City hosting. (Circa 1998) This would not have been my original site that I setup, but it is still old and crappy. My little home on the internet at that time was
http://www.fortunecity.com/tatooine/swampthing/104/ (Site predates the Internet Wayback Machine, so obviously dead link!)
This looks like an EARLY attempt to create a blog, before I even knew what a blog was.</description></item><item><title>Shutting down Blogspot</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/shutting-down-blogspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 01:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/shutting-down-blogspot/</guid><description>So, after a full year on this new blog I have decided to get rid of the old blog&amp;hellip;
I started amanoj.blogspot.com in July of 2003. Back then, I was still &amp;ldquo;Wet-Behind-the-Ears&amp;rdquo; about the whole blogging thing&amp;hellip; but I decided to give it a shot. Who knew that 6 years later, I would still be updating a site from time to time.
Blogger.com is a fantastic service for people who are just starting out (how I was) blogging.</description></item><item><title>Whats up all!!</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/whats-up-all/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 03:23:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/whats-up-all/</guid><description>I am still here. Thankfully my hosting company got their act&amp;rsquo;s together, and now we have plenty of bandwith to support this blog. Recently post have been just my Delicious bookmarks, which are posted to the blog on a nightly basis. (I will do a follow-up post on how to do that.)
Just an update of what I am working on&amp;hellip;
Upgrading our BlueCoat SG Proxy from an SG400 to a SG510.</description></item><item><title>Lets try that again...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/lets-try-that-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 07:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/lets-try-that-again/</guid><description>I am happy to announce the re-opening of this blog! ~w00t! :)
A special Thank You to my new provider Hosting Puppy for the site &amp;amp; the fantastic support.
After 3 unsuccessful hosting providers and 2 site-wide data corruption issues, one would think that I would learn from my mistakes.
Oh well, 4th times the charm!
The only good news is that I am now extremely perficent at re-building my Wordpress site.</description></item><item><title>March 2008 Update</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/march-08-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/march-08-update/</guid><description>Havent updated this in a while&amp;hellip; but I promise to add more content!
Just as an FYI of what I have been working on in the past 6 - 9 months:
Implementing a 300+ user Asterisk Implementation Re-vising the companies SOX controls. Creating new IT Procedures, revising old ones. Finishing up a massive NetBackup deployment. Completing an Internal Process Walkthrough. (One every year!) Planning our VMWare V3i implementation. Trying to stay afloat!</description></item><item><title>Launched a new blog...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2006/launched-a-new-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2006 04:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2006/launched-a-new-blog/</guid><description>With my good friend, we have decided to lauch a new team blog that focuses on technology knowledge sharing. Both of us are IT Professionals, and have many years experience. Instead of being greedy and not sharing, we decided to listen to Tux &amp;amp; share the wealth of knowledge to the public.
So check it out&amp;hellip; its called &amp;ldquo;Communication Meltdown&amp;rdquo; and its LIVE!!
I will still be posting on this blog, but most of the technical stuff will be posted on the new blog.</description></item><item><title>I'm Back!!</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2005/i-am-back/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2005 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2005/i-am-back/</guid><description>Its been awhile&amp;hellip; and all I can say is Im Back!
I have been extremely busy for the past year, what with the massive undertaking of my Companies Sarbanes-Oxley compliance, and managing the entire department while our new Director got up to speed. Not an easy task!
But now I&amp;rsquo;m back&amp;hellip; and I plan to put this blog to good use!
So&amp;hellip; to start of on the right foot, I am going to be documenting one of my many projects:</description></item><item><title>VisitorVille</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2004/visitorville/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2004 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2004/visitorville/</guid><description>This thing is pretty cool.. check it out. VisitorVille Will need to update the website to include this!</description></item></channel></rss>