<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Games on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/categories/games/</link><description>Recent content in Games on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 02:35:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nixdevil.com/categories/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WoW Emergent Media Phenomenon @ Laguna Art Museum</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/wow-emergent-media-phenomenon-at-laguna-art-museum/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 02:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/wow-emergent-media-phenomenon-at-laguna-art-museum/</guid><description>There is an interesting even being held at the Laguna Arts Museum in Laguna Beach. From June 14th to Oct 4th 2009, the museum is hosting a Art Exhibit on the Emergent Media Phenomenon of World of Warcraft . Normally I would say that this type of even it usually only appreciated by the fans of World of Warcraft (like me), but I think that anyone with a eye for decent art would appreciate it.</description></item><item><title>CFW 5.00 M33 to 5.50 GEN-B</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/cfw-5-00-m33-to-5-50-gen-b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 14:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/cfw-5-00-m33-to-5-50-gen-b/</guid><description>Not sure if this works, but I am destined to try!
Seems like newer games are requiring the 5.50 firmware, but I am still running CFW 5.00 M33! Where the hell is Dark-Alex gone to?
Oh well&amp;hellip; for your viewing pleasure!
The instructions in the comments are pretty decent. If you need your PSP to be running Custom Firmware&amp;hellip; let me know.</description></item><item><title>Summer Games...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/summer-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 20:44:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/summer-games/</guid><description>I have been a huge fan of Alternative Reality Games (ARG) for some time now. Ever since my first romp through EA&amp;rsquo;s Majestic (Which I still think is Ground-Breaking), and Lurking (read: following) on the I Love Bees games&amp;hellip; I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to stop!
I have participated &amp;amp; lurked quite a lot over the years&amp;hellip; some stories turn out to be very exciting, others have ended off shortly. I think there is a fine art to crafting a good ARG.</description></item><item><title>God of War 3 is Coming!!!</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/god-of-war-iii-is-coming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 03:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/god-of-war-iii-is-coming/</guid><description>I cant wait! I loved God of War I &amp;amp; II on the PS2, and was really impressed with God of War: Chains of Olympus on PSP.
I had passed on buying a PS3 at launch in 2006, only to buy a much cheaper Xbox 360. I still like my 360, and their are more games out for the platform&amp;hellip; but I knew that one day I would have to get the PS3 as well.</description></item></channel></rss>