<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>asterisk on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/asterisk/</link><description>Recent content in asterisk on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 19:51:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/asterisk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>plumTrack - A intresting new project from the Systrax team...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/plumtrack-a-intresting-new-project-from-the-systrax-team/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 19:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2009/plumtrack-a-intresting-new-project-from-the-systrax-team/</guid><description>Jo-G of Systrax Blog posted an article today on one of their many upcomming projects that they have been working on. plumTrack seems to provide some intresting reporting options for the Open Source PBX software Asterisk. The product also provides integration to Plixer&amp;rsquo;s own Scrutinizer gadgets, and Maximizer Enterprise CRM products.
Excerpt from the post&amp;hellip;
We have developed a Call Tracking system to monitor and report statistics of our Sales and Technical Support phone activity on our[Asterisk PBX](http://www.</description></item><item><title>Digium AsteriskWorld 2008</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/asteriskworld2008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/asteriskworld2008/</guid><description>Digium AsteriskWorld (Part of the VON.x Conference)
This has been a fun event so far. We have been fed on a regular basis, and Pulvermedia has sprung for the Top-Shelf Liquor. I did get to spend a lot of time with Marc Spencer w/ Digium. Great guy, and soooo damn young! I have a few more hours here before catching a plane, so lets see what-else this conference has in store.</description></item><item><title>Road to AsteriskWorld</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/road-2-asteriskworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/road-2-asteriskworld/</guid><description>One other thing. I am going to be in the San Jose area next-week for the AsteriskWorld convention.
Its going to be a fun time, and I am hoping to meet some like-minded individuals! (Networking Rocks!)
BTW&amp;hellip; I am posting more of my ramblings on my Twitter page! Please feel free to join my ring, and I will join yours! (We can all play nice right?)</description></item><item><title>March 2008 Update</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/march-08-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/2008/march-08-update/</guid><description>Havent updated this in a while&amp;hellip; but I promise to add more content!
Just as an FYI of what I have been working on in the past 6 - 9 months:
Implementing a 300+ user Asterisk Implementation Re-vising the companies SOX controls. Creating new IT Procedures, revising old ones. Finishing up a massive NetBackup deployment. Completing an Internal Process Walkthrough. (One every year!) Planning our VMWare V3i implementation. Trying to stay afloat!</description></item></channel></rss>