<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vmware on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/vmware/</link><description>Recent content in vmware on A haven for Unix &amp; Linux deviants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 22:16:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nixdevil.com/tags/vmware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vista x64 Uninstall VMware vCenter Converter Standalone</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/vista-x64-uninstall-vmware-vcenter-converter-standalone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 22:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/vista-x64-uninstall-vmware-vcenter-converter-standalone/</guid><description>If you are using Vista x64 and are trying to uninstall VMware vCenter Converter Standalone like I was, you may run into the following issue uninstalling&amp;hellip;
Error 1321. The Installer has insufficient privileges to modify the file C:\ProgramData\VMware\VMWare vCenter Converter Standalone\ssl\rui.key This aparently is due to a permissions issue on the following file:
C:\ProgramData\VMware\VMWare vCenter Converter Standalone\ssl\rui.key The minute you give yourself permissions to that file, you then can successfully uninstall it.</description></item><item><title>Still Here People...</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/still-here-people/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 01:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/still-here-people/</guid><description>Yep, I am still here on this site. I was having a few problems with my webhost earlier this month, but those should all be resolved by now. (I hope!)
Whats new in my life you ask&amp;hellip; well lets see:
Completed a Data Center re-cabling job in less than 72 hours! That was no easy feat, involving most of my staff to give up a weekend to get it done.</description></item><item><title>March 2008 Update</title><link>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/march-08-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nixdevil.com/posts/march-08-update/</guid><description>Havent updated this in a while&amp;hellip; but I promise to add more content!
Just as an FYI of what I have been working on in the past 6 - 9 months:
Implementing a 300+ user Asterisk Implementation Re-vising the companies SOX controls. Creating new IT Procedures, revising old ones. Finishing up a massive NetBackup deployment. Completing an Internal Process Walkthrough. (One every year!) Planning our VMWare V3i implementation. Trying to stay afloat!</description></item></channel></rss>